<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Books on</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/</link><description>Recent content in Books on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://j-entra.github.io/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/You-Are-a-Badass-at-Making-Money/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/You-Are-a-Badass-at-Making-Money/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Jen Sincero]] %% You Are a Badass at Making Money [[Jen Sincero]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] You have one glorious and brief shot at being the you that is you on Planet Earth, and the power to create whatever reality you desire. Why not be the biggest, happiest, most generous, and fully realized humanoid you can be?</description></item><item><title>1Q84</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/1Q84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/1Q84/</guid><description>[[haruki-murakami]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes See Also</description></item><item><title>A Short History of Nearly Everything</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/history-of-nearly-everything/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/history-of-nearly-everything/</guid><description>[[Bill Bryson]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes See Also</description></item><item><title>A-New-Earth</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/a-new-earth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/a-new-earth/</guid><description>[[eckhart-tolle]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes This is because it is still part of the same dysfunction, a more subtle and rarefied form of self enhancement, of desire for more and a strengthening of ones conceptual identity, ones self?image.
Everything, a bird, a tree, even a simple stone, and certainly a human being, is ultimately unknowable. This is because it has unfathomable depth. All we can perceive, experience, think about, is the surface layer of reality, less than the tip of an iceberg.</description></item><item><title>Atomic Habits</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/atomic-habits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/atomic-habits/</guid><description>[[James Clear]]
Concepts 1% better everyday. You don&amp;rsquo;t rise to the level of your goals, you fall to the level of your systems Build your identity, not your habits. Make ideal habits obvious, easy, attractive. Break habits by making it invisible, unattractive, difficult, and unsatisfying. Tools [[habit-stacking]] Thoughts Quotes The more pride you have in a particular aspect of your identity, the more motivated you will be to maintain the habits associated with it.</description></item><item><title>Awaken the Giant Within</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/awaken-the-giant-within/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/awaken-the-giant-within/</guid><description>[[Tony Robbins]]
Concepts Decisions determine destiny Rewrite pain and pleasure. Direct yourself Quotes sense of contribution, of knowing that we have made a difference in other people’s lives.
Man is not the creature of circumstances; circumstances are the creatures of men.”
Remember: Success truly is the result of good judgment. Good judgment is the result of experience, and experience is often the result of bad judgment!</description></item><item><title>Breaking the Habit of Being Yourself</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/breaking-the-habit-of-being-yourself/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/breaking-the-habit-of-being-yourself/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Joe Dispenza]] %% Breaking the Habit of Being Yourself [[Joe Dispenza]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] When you overcome your senses, when you understand that you are not bound by the chains of your past—when you live a life that is greater than your body, your environment, and time—all things are possible.
See Also</description></item><item><title>Circe</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Circe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Circe/</guid><description> index &amp;lt; 1-library [[Madeline Miller]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] See Also</description></item><item><title>Creativity - Flow</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Creativity-Flow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Creativity-Flow/</guid><description>Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes In other words, creativity is more likely in places where new ideas require less effort to be perceived.
“It makes the spirit sing,”
The fact that calculus and Gregorian chants exist means that we can experience patterns of order that were not programmed into our genes by biological evolution. By learning the rules of a domain, we immediately step beyond the boundaries of biology and enter the realm of cultural evolution.</description></item><item><title>Deep Work</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Deep-Work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Deep-Work/</guid><description>[[Cal Newport]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes they were instead happier because they had rewired their brains to ignore the negative and savor the positive.
“The best moments usually occur when a person’s body or mind is stretched to its limits in a voluntary effort to accomplish something difficult and worthwhile.”
“I’ll live the focused life, because it’s the best kind there is.”
A deep life is a good life, any way you look at it.</description></item><item><title>Discipline Equals Freedom</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Discipline-Equals-Freedom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Discipline-Equals-Freedom/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Jocko Willink]] %% Discipline Equals Freedom [[Jocko Willink]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] Because The Warpath is also a war against weakness— and so it leads to strength.
That guy thinks a positive attitude will solve problems. It won’t. But neither will dwelling on the problem.
Convinced to take an easier path. Enticed by comfort.</description></item><item><title>Dont Make Me Think, Revisited</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Dont-Make-Me-Think-Revisited/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Dont-Make-Me-Think-Revisited/</guid><description>[[Steve Krug]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes it’s short, it’s more likely to actually be used. See Also</description></item><item><title>Essentialism</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Essentialism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Essentialism/</guid><description>[[Greg Mckeown]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Less but better.
“Tell me, what is it you plan to do / with your one wild and precious life?”
“A strategic position is not sustainable unless there are trade-offs with other positions.”
He then informed them that they were all wrong. The lead to the story, he said, was “There will be no school Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Getting Things Done</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Getting-Things-Done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Getting-Things-Done/</guid><description>[[David Allen]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Anxiety is caused by a lack of control, organization, preparation, and action.
The answer is, totally appropriately to the force and mass of the input; then it returns to calm. It doesn’t overreact or underreact.
If your mind is empty, it is always ready for anything; it is open to everything.
First of all, if it’s on your mind, your mind isn’t clear.</description></item><item><title>Great Thinkers</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Great-Thinkers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Great-Thinkers/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book #on/philosophy dates: people: [[the-school-of-life]] %% [[the-school-of-life]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Behind the fantasy of luxury, what he believed we really want is calm.
But our reasoned intelligence can give us unique access to another perspective. It can quite literally allow us – here Spinoza becomes beautifully lyrical – to participate in eternal totality.
‘If there is a sin against life, it consists perhaps not so much in despairing of life as in hoping for another life and in eluding the implacable grandeur of this life.</description></item><item><title>High Performance Habits</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/High-Performance-Habits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/High-Performance-Habits/</guid><description>[[Brendon Burchard]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes “Whatever I have tried to do in life, I have tried with all my heart to do it well; whatever I have devoted myself to, I have devoted myself to completely.”
“The quality of a person’s life is in direct proportion to their commitment to excellence, regardless of their chosen field of endeavor.” —Vince Lombardi It
In fact, most want to meet their deadlines because they’re excited to see their work out there in the world, as well as to move on to the next project or opportunity they have chosen for themselves.</description></item><item><title>Homo Deus</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Homo-Deus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Homo-Deus/</guid><description>[[Yuval-Noah-Harari]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes A large part of our artistic creativity, our political commitment and our religious piety is fuelled by the fear of death See Also</description></item><item><title>how to read a book</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/how-to-read-a-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/how-to-read-a-book/</guid><description>index &amp;lt;</description></item><item><title>how to take smart notes</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/how-to-take-smart-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/how-to-take-smart-notes/</guid><description>Sonke Ahrens
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes See Also</description></item><item><title>How to Think Like Leonardo da Vinci</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/How-to-Think-Like-Leonardo-da-Vinci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/How-to-Think-Like-Leonardo-da-Vinci/</guid><description>[[Michael J. Gelb]]
[[1-concepts]] [[curiosity]]
[[When am I most naturally myself?]] [[What is the one thing I could stop doing, or start doing, or do differently, starting today that would most improve the quality of my life?]] [[What is my greatest talent?]] [[How can I get paid for doing what I love?]] [[Who are my most inspiring role models?]] [[How can I best be of service to others?]] [[What is my heart&amp;rsquo;s deepest desire?</description></item><item><title>How-to-Think-More-Effectively</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/How-to-Think-More-Effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/How-to-Think-More-Effectively/</guid><description>[[the-school-of-life]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Acknowledging the unfair bias, we should strive to ensure that at least 20% of our efforts is henceforth devoted to reflecting on the deeper ‘why’ questions before we allow ourselves to ‘relax’ into the more familiar and more routine work of execution.
A talented artist is, first and foremost, someone who takes us into the specifics of valuable experiences.
See Also</description></item><item><title>Illusions The Adventures of a Reluctant Messiah</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Illusions-The-Adventures-of-a-Reluctant-Messiah/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Illusions-The-Adventures-of-a-Reluctant-Messiah/</guid><description>[[Richard Bach]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Argue for your limitations, and sure enough, they&amp;rsquo;re yours.
want to remove a cloud from your life, you do not make a big production out of it, you just relax and remove it from your thinking.
See Also</description></item><item><title>Jade City</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Jade-City/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Jade-City/</guid><description>[[Fonda Lee]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Summer had barely begun and already the city of Janloon was like a spent lover—sticky and fragrant.
Far out on the water, the slowly traveling lights of shipping vessels were smeared into blotches by sea fog and the haze of pollution from the city.
The air was warm and heavy with fumes, the sweetness of overripe fruit, and the stink of nine hundred thousand perspiring inhabitants.</description></item><item><title>Kafka on the Shore</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Kafka-on-the-Shore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Kafka-on-the-Shore/</guid><description>[[haruki-murakami]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;In traveling, a companion, in life, compassion,'&amp;rdquo; she repeats, making sure of it. If she had paper and pencil, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise me if she wrote it down. &amp;ldquo;So what does that really mean? In simple terms.&amp;rdquo; I think it over. It takes me a while to gather my thoughts, but she waits patiently. &amp;ldquo;I think it means,&amp;rdquo; I say, &amp;ldquo;that chance encounters are what keep us going.</description></item><item><title>Life of Pi</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Life-of-Pi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Life-of-Pi/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Yann Martel]] %% Life of Pi [[Yann Martel]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] To choose doubt as a philosophy of life is akin to choosing immobility as a means of transportation. See Also</description></item><item><title>Mans Search for Meaning</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Mans-Search-for-Meaning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Mans-Search-for-Meaning/</guid><description>[[Viktor Frankl]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] See Also</description></item><item><title>Mastery</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Mastery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Mastery/</guid><description>Robert Greene Concepts [[flow-state]] [[knowledge-power]] [[1-self-knowledge]] [[Your interest must transcend the field itself and border on the religious.]] [[pleasure-of-challenge]] [[hacker-apprenticeship]]
Tools for Finding Your Life Task [[private/¶-primal-inclination-strategy]] [[darwinian-strategy]] [[ideal-apprenticeship]] Thoughts Counter-forces have been present, but I hardly think I have followed them. Everything that I have done is a result of my own actions, and even a lack of following the call to action.
The field that sparks the &amp;ldquo;childlike sense of wonder and excitement&amp;rdquo; will allow you to learn with a sense of urgency and necessity.</description></item><item><title>Meditations</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Meditations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Meditations/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book #on/philosophy #on/stoicism dates: people: [[Emperor of Rome Marcus Aurelius]] %% Meditations [[Emperor of Rome Marcus Aurelius]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] Desire and dislike, opinion and affection, are within the power of the will; whereas health, wealth, honour, and other such are generally not so.
He drills his soul, as it were, in right principles, that when the time comes, it may be guided by them.</description></item><item><title>No Excuses!</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/No-Excuses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/No-Excuses/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Tracy, Brian]] %% No Excuses! [[Tracy, Brian]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] The more you practice self-mastery and self-control, the more you like and value yourself; • The more you discipline yourself, the greater is your sense of self-respect and personal pride; • The more you practice self-discipline, the better is your self-image. You see yourself and think about yourself in a more positive way.</description></item><item><title>Raise Your Game</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Raise-Your-Game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Raise-Your-Game/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Alan Stein]] %% Raise Your Game [[Alan Stein]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] A coach should build a work environment where everyone is able to achieve both their highest selves, as well as what is best for the team.
“You just have to crave the end result so intensely that the hard work is irrelevant.”</description></item><item><title>Sapiens</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Sapiens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Sapiens/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Yuval-Noah-Harari]] %% Sapiens [[Yuval-Noah-Harari]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] A colt can trot shortly after birth; a kitten leaves its mother to forage on its own when it is just a few weeks old. Human babies are helpless, dependent for many years on their elders for sustenance, protection and education.
Humans emerge from the womb like molten glass from a furnace.</description></item><item><title>Secret of the Ages</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Secret-of-the-Ages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Secret-of-the-Ages/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Carol Rosselle]] %% Secret of the Ages [[Carol Rosselle]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] But obstacles, misfortunes, cataclysms, were to it merely new opportunities to assert its power. In fact, it required obstacles to awaken it, to show its energy and resource.
the whole purpose of existence is GROWTH.
“It matters not how strait the gate, How charged with punishment the scroll, I am the Master of my Fate; I am the Captain of my Soul.</description></item><item><title>show your work</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/show-your-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/show-your-work/</guid><description> index &amp;lt; learn in public You don’t have to be a genius. Think process, not product. Share something small every day. Open up your cabinet of curiosities. Tell good stories. Teach what you know. Don’t turn into human spam. Learn to take a punch. Sell out. Stick around.</description></item><item><title>Steve Jobs</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Steve-Jobs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/Steve-Jobs/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Walter Isaacson]] %% Steve Jobs [[Walter Isaacson]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] he said that religion was at its best when it emphasized spiritual experiences rather than received
See Also</description></item><item><title>Tao Te Ching</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/tao-te-ching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/tao-te-ching/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The 15 Invaluable Laws of Growth</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-15-Invaluable-Laws-of-Growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-15-Invaluable-Laws-of-Growth/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[John Maxwell]] %% The 15 Invaluable Laws of Growth [[John Maxwell]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes “If you are clear with what you want, the world responds with clarity.”
attitude, goals, discipline, measurement, and consistency.
“Life lived for tomorrow will always be a day away from being realized.”
you want to reach your potential and become the person you were created to be, you must do much more than just experience life and hope that you learn what you need along the way.</description></item><item><title>The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-7-Habits-of-Highly-Effective-People/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-7-Habits-of-Highly-Effective-People/</guid><description>[[Stephen R. Covey]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes We see the world, not as it is, but as we are—or, as we are conditioned to see it.
But each person’s interpretation of these facts represents prior experiences, and the facts have no meaning whatsoever apart from the interpretation.
Between stimulus and response, man has the freedom to choose.
Their behavior is a product of their own conscious choice, based on values, rather</description></item><item><title>The Defining Decade</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Defining-Decade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Defining-Decade/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Meg Jay]] %% The Defining Decade [[Meg Jay]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] “The art of being wise is knowing what to overlook.”
if we externalize our distress too much, we don’t learn to handle bad days on our own.
See Also</description></item><item><title>The Four Agreements</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Four-Agreements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Four-Agreements/</guid><description>[[Don Miguel Ruiz]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes We never had the opportunity to choose what to believe or what not to believe. We never chose even the smallest of these agreements. We didn’t even choose our own name.
The outside dream may hook our attention, but if we don’t agree, we don’t store that information. As soon as we agree, we believe it, and this is called faith.</description></item><item><title>The Magic of Thinking Big</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Magic-of-Thinking-Big/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Magic-of-Thinking-Big/</guid><description>[[David J. Schwartz]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes A person who thinks his job is important Receives mental signals on how to do his job better; And a better job means More promotions, more money, more prestige, more happiness.
Think enthusiastically. Build in yourself an optimistic, progressive glow, a feeling that “this is great and I’m 100 percent for it.”
Grow the attitude of I’m activated.</description></item><item><title>The Mistborn Trilogy</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Mistborn-Trilogy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Mistborn-Trilogy/</guid><description>[[Brandon Sanderson]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes See Also</description></item><item><title>The Power of Full Engagement</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Power-of-Full-Engagement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Power-of-Full-Engagement/</guid><description>[[James E. Loehr]] [[Tony Schwartz]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Most of us spend more time reacting to immediate crises and responding to the expectations of others than we do making considered choices guided by a clear sense of what matters most.
smoking or drinking to manage anxiety; furiously multitasking to meet demands; setting aside more challenging,
&amp;ldquo;There isn&amp;rsquo;t anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t made easier through constant familiarity and training.</description></item><item><title>The Power of Now</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/power-of-now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/power-of-now/</guid><description>[[Eckhart Tolle]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes It is not a trancelike state. Not at all. There is no loss of consciousness here. The opposite is the case. If the price of peace were a lowering of your consciousness, and the price of stillness a lack of vitality and alertness, then they would not be worth having.
you are much more alert, more awake than in the mind-identified state.</description></item><item><title>the republic</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/the-republic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/the-republic/</guid><description> index &amp;lt; interests &amp;lt; literature deals with:
best life for a being what kind of society would grant that best life? justice is whatever happens to be in the interest of the stronger</description></item><item><title>The Secret</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Secret/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Secret/</guid><description>%%
metadata tags: #source/book dates: people: [[Ronda Byrne]] %% The Secret [[Ronda Byrne]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes recommends at the end of every day, before you go to sleep, to think through the events of the day. If any events or moments did not go the way you wanted, replay them in your mind in a way that thrills you.
When you allow a thought of doubt to enter your mind, the law of attraction will soon line up one doubtful thought after another.</description></item><item><title>The Talent Code</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Talent-Code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Talent-Code/</guid><description>[[Daniel Coyle]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Deep practice is built on a paradox: struggling in certain targeted ways—operating at the edges of your ability, where you make mistakes—makes you smarter. Or to put it a slightly different way, experiences where you&amp;rsquo;re forced to slow down, make errors, and correct them—as
This is why many successful ads involve some degree of cognitive work,
Sven Anders Hedin, Scandinavia&amp;rsquo;s turn-of-the-century version of Indiana Jones.</description></item><item><title>The War Of Art</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-War-Of-Art/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-War-Of-Art/</guid><description>[[Steven Pressfield]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes He endowed each of us with our own unique genius. See Also</description></item><item><title>The-Essence-of-Jungs-Psychology-and-Tibetan-Buddhism</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Essence-of-Jungs-Psychology-and-Tibetan-Buddhism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/The-Essence-of-Jungs-Psychology-and-Tibetan-Buddhism/</guid><description>[[{{author}}]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes See Also</description></item><item><title>This Is Marketing</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/This-Is-Marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/This-Is-Marketing/</guid><description>[[Seth Godin]]
[[1-concepts]] Tools Thoughts [[Quotes]] Ideas that spread, win.
Desire for gain versus avoidance of loss.
The way we make things better is by caring enough about those we serve to imagine the story that they need to hear.
See Also</description></item><item><title>What I Talk About When I Talk About Running</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/What-I-Talk-About-When-I-Talk-About-Running/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/What-I-Talk-About-When-I-Talk-About-Running/</guid><description>[[haruki-murakami]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes See Also</description></item><item><title>Σ be here now</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/be-here-now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/be-here-now/</guid><description>index &amp;lt; 1-library [[Ram Dass]]
Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes To become free of attachment means to break the link identifying you with your desires. The desires continue; they are part of the dance of nature. But a renunciate no longer thinks that he is his desires.
As many times as you trip and fall, i.e., give in to a desire—just get up.
think upon pouring God into God, if you know what I mean.</description></item><item><title>Σ cant hurt me</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/books/cant-hurt-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/books/cant-hurt-me/</guid><description>index &amp;lt; 1-library Concepts Tools Thoughts Quotes Maybe your limiting factor is that you grew up so supported and comfortable, you never pushed yourself?
Tell the truth about the real reasons for your limitations and you will turn that negativity, which is real, into jet fuel.
But when you have no confidence it becomes easy to value other people’s opinions, and I was valuing everyone’s opinion without considering the minds that generated them.</description></item></channel></rss>