<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>atom on</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/tags/atom/</link><description>Recent content in atom on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://j-entra.github.io/tags/atom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1% better everyday</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/one-percent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/one-percent/</guid><description/></item><item><title>niagara syndrome</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/niagara-syndrome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/niagara-syndrome/</guid><description> index &amp;lt; Awaken the Giant Within if life is a river, people jump into it headfirst without knowing exactly where to go and what to do. so they get caught up in the &amp;ldquo;current&amp;rdquo; — current events, current fears, current challenges. tao te ching we are out of our control — everything else controls us solution: direct yourself by making a decision decisions determine destiny</description></item><item><title>save what speaks</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/save-what-speaks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/save-what-speaks/</guid><description>save what speaks, speak what you save.
insights should be relevant, not verbatim. do not attempt to glean information that you think the author is trying to tell you but rather see what directly applies to you and your place in life. if you come across an #atom that wasn&amp;rsquo;t inherent in the original source, that is yours to keep.
in turn, you should share that original insight with your community #on/producing learn in public</description></item><item><title>The reward of simplicity comes after the toil of complexity.</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/complexity-then-simplicity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/complexity-then-simplicity/</guid><description>index Notes : &amp;ldquo;I draw same conclusion as you though. Can&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;skip&amp;rdquo; the middle. But not because it&amp;rsquo;s some &amp;ldquo;love the journey&amp;rdquo; thing or &amp;ldquo;the accomplishment is the journey&amp;rdquo;, but rather because you just can&amp;rsquo;t tell people stuff. They have to feel it themselves. apprenticeship matters.
To me simplicity is made more beautiful when understood through a long personal struggle with complexity. When I can dance with it, having turned a mighty nemesis into an old friend, and teach others to do the same.</description></item></channel></rss>