<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thesaurus on</title><link>https://j-entra.github.io/thesaurus/</link><description>Recent content in Thesaurus on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://j-entra.github.io/thesaurus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Assail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Assail/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Assail Meanings Verb Make a concerted or violent attack on.
the Scots army assailed Edward&amp;rsquo;s army from the rear
attack, assault, make an assault on, launch an attack on, pounce on, set upon, launch oneself at, weigh into, fly at, let fly at, turn on, round on, lash out at, hit out at, beset, belabour, fall on, accost, mug, charge, rush, storm, besiege</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Coarsen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Coarsen/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Coarsen Meanings Verb Make or become rough.
her hands were coarsened by outside work
roughen, thicken, toughen, harden
Make or become vulgar or unpleasant.
her experience has not coarsened her or made her cynical
desensitize, harshen, dehumanize</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Confer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Confer/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Confer Meanings Verb Grant (a title, degree, benefit, or right)
the Minister may have exceeded the powers conferred on him by Parliament
bestow on, present to, present with, grant to, award to, decorate with, honour with, give to, give out to, gift with, endow with, vest in, hand out to, extend to, vouchsafe to, accord to
Have discussions; exchange opinions.
the officials were conferring with allies</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Corollary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Corollary/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Corollary Meanings Noun A proposition that follows from (and is often appended to) one already proved.
For these angles, the contradiction used to prove the corollary does not arise.
Adjective Forming a proposition that follows from one already proved.
The British journal New Theatre Quarterly has even run a series of articles discussing the theatricality of the uncertainty principle and corollary axioms.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Corpulent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Corpulent/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Corpulent Meanings Adjective (of a person) fat.
a short, somewhat corpulent man
fat, fattish, obese, overweight, plump, portly, stout, chubby, paunchy, beer-bellied, thickset, hefty, heavy, heavyset, burly, bulky, chunky, well padded, well covered, well upholstered, meaty, fleshy, rotund, round, well rounded, broad, broad in the beam, of ample proportions, big, large, gargantuan, elephantine</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Cosseted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Cosseted/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Cosseted Meanings Adjective Cared for and protected in an overindulgent way; pampered.
the cosseted daughter of an upper-class New England family
pamper, indulge, overindulge, mollycoddle, coddle, baby, pet, mother, nanny, nursemaid, pander to, spoon-feed, overparent, spoil
like Cosset from [[Les Misérables]]</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Dearth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Dearth/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Dearth Meanings Noun A scarcity or lack of something.
there is a dearth of evidence
lack, scarcity, scarceness, shortage, shortfall, want, deficiency, insufficiency, inadequacy, paucity, sparseness, meagreness, scantiness, rareness, infrequency, uncommonness, destitution, privation</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Deference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Deference/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Deference Meanings Noun Humble submission and respect.
he addressed her with the deference due to age
respect, respectfulness, regard, esteem</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Diaphanous/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Diaphanous/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Diaphanous Meanings Adjective (especially of fabric) light, delicate, and translucent.
a diaphanous dress of pale gold
sheer, fine, ultra-fine, delicate, light, lightweight, thin, insubstantial, floaty, flimsy, filmy, silken, chiffony, gossamer, gossamery, gossamer-thin, gossamer-like, gauzy, gauze-like, cobwebby, feathery</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Esoteric/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Esoteric/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Esoteric Meanings Adjective Intended for or likely to be understood by only a small number of people with a specialized knowledge or interest.
esoteric philosophical debates
abstruse, obscure, arcane, recherché, rarefied, recondite, abstract, difficult, hard, puzzling, perplexing, enigmatic, inscrutable, cryptic, Delphic</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Flout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Flout/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Flout Meanings Transitive Verb Openly disregard (a rule, law or convention)
these same companies still flout basic ethical practices
defy, refuse to obey, go against, rebel against, scorn, disdain, show contempt for, fly in the face of, thumb one&amp;rsquo;s nose at, make a fool of, poke fun at</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Gall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Gall/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Gall Meanings Noun Bold and impudent behaviour.
the bank had the gall to demand a fee
impudence, insolence, impertinence, cheek, cheekiness, nerve, audacity, brazenness, effrontery, temerity, presumption, presumptuousness, brashness, shamelessness, pertness, boldness
The contents of the gall bladder; bile (proverbial for its bitterness).
In central Ontario, eight species of parasitoids and a Periclistus inquiline are associated with this gall.
acrimony, resentment, rancour, sourness, acerbity, asperity</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Indomitable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Indomitable/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Indomitable Meanings Adjective Impossible to subdue or defeat.
a woman of indomitable spirit
invincible, unconquerable, unbeatable, unassailable, impregnable, invulnerable, unsurpassable, unshakeable
can&amp;rsquo;t dominate</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Insipid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Insipid/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Insipid Meanings Adjective Lacking flavor.
mugs of insipid coffee
tasteless, flavourless, unflavoured, savourless, bland, weak, thin, watery, watered-down, unappetizing, unpalatable</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Inviolable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Inviolable/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Inviolable Meanings Adjective Never to be broken, infringed, or dishonored.
an inviolable rule of chastity
inalienable, absolute, untouchable, unalterable, unchallengeable, unbreakable, impregnable
not violated-able</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Kowtow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Kowtow/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Kowtow Meanings Intransitive Verb Act in an excessively subservient manner.
she didn&amp;rsquo;t have to kowtow to a boss
grovel, behave obsequiously, be obsequious, be servile, be sycophantic, fawn on, bow and scrape, toady, truckle, abase oneself, humble oneself, prostrate oneself
Kneel and touch the ground with the forehead in worship or submission as part of Chinese custom.
In ‘Keeper of the Keys,’ Chan has to deal with a much older Chinese servant who kowtows to his white master in embarrassing fashion.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Levant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Levant/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Levant Meanings Intransitive Verb Run away, typically leaving unpaid debts.
the clerk had levanted before his employer returned from America
withdraw, retire, draw back, pull back, pull out, fall back, give way, give ground, recoil, flee, take flight, beat a retreat, beat a hasty retreat, run away, run off, make a run for it, run for it, make off, take off, take to one&amp;rsquo;s heels, make a break for it, bolt, make a quick exit, clear out, make one&amp;rsquo;s getaway, escape, head for the hills</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Maelstrom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Maelstrom/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Maelstrom Meanings Noun A powerful whirlpool in the sea or a river.
Together they stood in the foretops and conned the ship in through the seething maelstrom of the equatorial current.
whirlpool, vortex, eddy, swirl
mal - storm</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Mollify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Mollify/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Mollify Meanings Transitive Verb Appease the anger or anxiety of (someone)
nature reserves were set up around the power stations to mollify local conservationists
appease, placate, pacify, conciliate, humour, soothe, calm, calm down, still, propitiate</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Overture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Overture/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Overture Meanings Noun An orchestral piece at the beginning of an opera, suite, play, oratorio, or other extended composition.
the overture to Mozart&amp;rsquo;s “Don Giovanni”
prelude, introduction, opening, introductory movement, voluntary
An introduction to something more substantial.
the talks were no more than an overture to a long debate
preliminary, prelude, curtain-raiser, introduction, lead-in, precursor, forerunner, harbinger, herald, start, beginning
An approach or proposal made to someone with the aim of opening negotiations or establishing a relationship.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Reproach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Reproach/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Reproach Meanings Transitive Verb Address (someone) in such a way as to express disapproval or disappointment.
“You know that isn&amp;rsquo;t true,” he reproached her
express a poor opinion of, have a poor opinion of, dislike, be against, object to, find unacceptable, think wrong, take exception to, not believe in, not support, frown on, take a dim view of, look askance at
Noun The expression of disapproval or disappointment.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Rote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Rote/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Rote Meanings Noun Mechanical or habitual repetition of something to be learned.
a poem learned by rote in childhood
mechanically, automatically, without thinking, unthinkingly, parrot-fashion, mindlessly</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Trepidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Trepidation/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Trepidation Meanings Noun A feeling of fear or agitation about something that may happen.
the men set off in fear and trepidation
fear, apprehension, dread, fearfulness, apprehensiveness, agitation, anxiety, worry, nervousness, tension, misgivings, unease, uneasiness, foreboding, disquiet, disquietude, perturbation, discomposure, dismay, consternation, alarm, panic, trembling, jumpiness
Trembling motion.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Venerable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://j-entra.github.io/Thesaurus/Venerable/</guid><description>[[Thesaurus]]
Venerable Meanings Adjective Accorded a great deal of respect, especially because of age, wisdom, or character.
a venerable statesman
respected, venerated, revered, reverenced, worshipped, honoured, esteemed, hallowed, august, distinguished, acclaimed, celebrated, lionized
the venerable</description></item></channel></rss>